It is also
very good, very good. So Anil ji, the
company's results are much better than expected. In
fact, when the
data of general insurance companies was coming, we had
seen that there was a continuous
increase in the premium income and in the
company's results, the
premium income has increased to 135. Not
only this, the claim ratio is continuously decreasing, it has remained
flat this time and the
expense ratio has decreased. So, obviously,
if your claim ratio, expense
ratio, all these things decrease, then it has a direct impact on the
company's profits. And that is what
we saw, where an increase of around 22 was seen. The
company had set a
target of 25 for the combined ratio of 102 here, the
company is running around that.
If you look at the return on average equity, then there has been an
increase in it also in this quarter.
It has increased from 14.3 to 15.3. So,
if you look at all the ratios, all of them
are indicating that the company
You may see good growth in the future. The
growth of the company has been quite good in this quarter as well. The
management
is also very confident about the future growth. Not only
this, brokerage houses are also confident about the growth of this company.
For this,
be it Goldman or CLS, both have
increased their targets. Goldman has
increased it from 1475 to 1500, CLSA has increased it from 1620 to
around 1650. So,
if you look at this, the entire nine months (5-24) have
also been good. The
trends that are coming till now regarding the growth of these companies are
also good.
For this, you are seeing a
good jump in the stock of this company after the results. We have
seen a big action after the results and
because of this,
you are seeing a good rise in the entire insurance space. IC
Lombard is still playing its
ball.